<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hussain Kadhem</title>
    <link>https://hussainjk.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hussain Kadhem</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>hussainmkj@gmail.com (Hussain Kadhem)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>hussainmkj@gmail.com (Hussain Kadhem)</webMaster>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hussainjk.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Disability Statement</title>
      <link>https://hussainjk.github.io/about/disability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hussainmkj@gmail.com (Hussain Kadhem)</author>
      <guid>https://hussainjk.github.io/about/disability/</guid>
      <description>I am almost completely blind from birth, due to a genetic disorder known as LCA. My vision is limited to light levels and silhouettes of large objects, and there are a variety of resources I use to compensate for this. The most important of these being, of course, my own resourcefulness.
Screen Reader A screen reader is a piece of software which uses synthesized speech to read aloud the contents of computer applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Otter</title>
      <link>https://hussainjk.github.io/about/otter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>hussainmkj@gmail.com (Hussain Kadhem)</author>
      <guid>https://hussainjk.github.io/about/otter/</guid>
      <description>Hi there! I am a yellow Labradore retriever, and for the past 4 years I have been providing guiding services to my client Hussain Kadhem. I graduated Summa cum laude in September 2016 from a two-year vocational training program at the Guide Dogs For the Blind school in San Rafael, California.
On My Work I work with my client on a daily basis to provide travel safety and navigation services. These involve taking point on negotiation of tough pedestrian and urban issues, such as phones claiming monopolies on the pedestrian attention market, and automobiles in teritorial disputes with sidewalks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>